Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ooh!
♪ 哦！
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob Squarepants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Ah...
啊...
I don't know how you do it,
Gar Bear.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
嘎尔熊.
But that's the best cup of
French toast I've ever had.
但这是最好的一杯
我吃过的法式吐司。
Well, time to punch that clock.
好吧，是时候打卡了。
But not before checking
但在检查之前没有
my motivational
quote-a-day calendar.
我的励志
每日报价日历。
"You are a winner."
“你是赢家。”
And today's the first day
of summer.
今天是第一天
夏天的。
Happy first day of summer,
Squidward.
暑假第一天快乐，
章鱼哥。
Care to join me for
solstice caroling?
关心和我一起
至日颂歌？
♪ Walking in the grass,
it's all fine ♪
♪ 漫步在草地上，
一切都好♪
♪ Don't need shoes
in the summertime ♪
♪ 不需要鞋子
夏天的时候♪
I'm not much of a summer person,
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Davy Jones on the jib!
戴维琼斯在三角帆上！
Do my ears deceive me?
难道是我的耳朵欺骗了我？
Is it really
the first day of summer?
真的是吗
夏天的第一天？
Is it?!
是吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Oo-whee-hoo!
哦呼呼！
Gee, Mr. K,
you sure have
哎呀，K先生，
你肯定有
a scorching case
of summer fever.
灼热的案件
夏季发烧。
What is it about summertime
夏天有什么讲究
that makes us so happy?
这让我们如此高兴？
The firefly-lit nights?
萤火虫点亮的夜晚？
The intoxicating aroma
of a charcoal briquette?
醉人的香气
木炭块？
The hypnotic sound of a lawn
mower running over a flip-flop?
草坪催眠的声音
割草机碾过人字拖？
The money.
钱。
The money?
钱？
Er, uh, I mean, uh...
the children.
呃，呃，我的意思是，呃...
孩子们。
Oh.
哦。
You see, boy, during the summer
你看，孩子，在夏天
the children are excused
from their classes.
孩子们被原谅了
从他们的班级。
A recess commonly
通常有一个休息时间
referred to as summer break.
简称暑假。
Tell me more about summer break.
告诉我更多关于暑假的事情。
Well, during the summer break
嗯，暑假期间
the children wander
Bikini Bottom unsupervised
孩子们徘徊
无人监管的比基尼泳裤
their pockets lined
with allowance
他们的口袋里有衬里
有津贴
free to spend their money
自由地花他们的钱
without any parental guidance
whatsoever.
没有任何家长指导
无论如何。
I guess that's what I like best.
我想这就是我最喜欢的。
Sure I suppose some would try
当然我想有些人会尝试
and take advantage
of this situation
并利用
这种情况的
by selling them toys or candy.
向他们出售玩具或糖果。
But I sleep well at night
with the knowledge
但我晚上睡得很好
与知识
that I'm providing them
with something they need...
我正在向他们提供
和他们需要的东西...
A nutritious meal.
营养丰富的一餐。
Come here, you little piggies!
过来吧，你们这些小猪们！
I've been taught the true
meaning of summer.
我被教导了真实的
夏天的意义。
Almost closing time,
Mr. K.
快到关门时间了，
K 先生
What?!
什么？！
But that's impossible!
但这是不可能的！
What about the money?!
钱呢？！
I mean, uh...
uh, what about the children?
我的意思是，呃...
呃，孩子们呢？
I guess summer isn't
coming this year.
我想夏天不是
今年即将到来。
Hey, maybe they're all
at that new playground
over there.
嘿，也许他们都是
在那个新游乐场
在那儿。
Playground?!
操场？！
Luring away me young customers?
引走我的年轻顾客？
Warm up the boat, SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝，给船预热。
See anything, Mr. Krabs?
看到什么了吗，蟹老板？
Oh, they're here all right.
哦，他们还在这里。
Just look at them, SpongeBob.
看看他们，海绵宝宝。
So weak and malnourished
如此虚弱且营养不良
with nobody trying
to sell them nothing.
没有人尝试
不向他们出售任何东西。
Breaks me heart.
让我心碎。
No!!
不！！
I got nothing to live
for, SpongeBob.
我没有什么可以活的
为了，海绵宝宝。
The way you drove the boat
你驾驶船的方式
belying on the ground
was kind of cool.
躺在地上
有点酷。
True.
真的。
But that's not going
to get these munchkins
但这不会发生
得到这些芒奇金人
away from this playground.
远离这个游乐场。
Unless...
除非...
Hmm.
唔。
See you tomorrow, boy.
明天见，男孩。
Got a lot of work to do.
有很多工作要做。
You got it, Mr. Krabs.
你明白了，蟹老板。
Hey!
嘿！
Another day, another dollar.
又一天，又一美元。
Gee, I wonder what Mr. Krabs has
been up to since I saw him last
哎呀，我想知道蟹老板有什么
自从我上次见到他以来一直在忙
and then went home to do
nothing of particular interest
然后回家做
没有什么特别感兴趣的
till this very moment.
直到这一刻。
Huh?!
啊？！
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
You're just in time for
the grand unveiling of...
你正好赶上
隆重揭幕...
Krabby Land.
克拉比土地。
Krabby Land, sir?
甲米地，先生？
Yes, Krabby Land.
是的，克拉比乐园。
Where a kid can have fun.
孩子们可以玩得开心的地方。
For the right price.
以合适的价格。
Welcome to the Krusty
Krab, young man.
欢迎来到库斯蒂
蟹蟹，年轻人。
What's your name?
你叫什么名字？
Monroe.
门罗。
Nice to meet you, Monroe.
很高兴认识你，门罗。
Whee!
哎哟！
Aha.
啊哈。
Okay, Money...
好吧，钱……
I mean, uh, children.
我的意思是，呃，孩子们。
It's time for the grand
unveiling of Money!
又到了盛大的时候了
金钱揭晓！
I mean, Krabby Land!
我是说，克拉比乐园！
Yay!
耶！
Okay, kids,
now promise Uncle Krabs
好吧，孩子们，
现在向蟹叔叔保证
that if you get hungry
while you're playing
如果你饿了
当你玩的时候
you'll come inside
for some delicious
你会进来的
一些美味的
nutritious Krabby Patties.
营养丰富的蟹黄饼。
We promise.
我们保证。
All right, here we go.
好吧，我们开始吧。
I give you... Krabby Land!
我给你...克拉比土地！
Yay!
耶！
Whoa! Ooh!
哇！哦！
Where am I?
我在哪里？
Uh... that reminds me.
呃……这让我想起了。
I forgot to give you
these coloring books
我忘了给你
这些涂色书
slash liability waivers.
大幅削减责任豁免。
Everyone who hands theirs back
每个归还自己的人
gets to meet the one and only
Krabby the Clown.
遇见唯一的一个
小丑克拉比。
Yay!
耶！
Have fun.
And don't forget to eat plenty
玩得开心。
并且不要忘记多吃
of vitamin-enriched
Krabby Patties...
富含维生素的
蟹黄饼...
Krabby the Clown's
favorite meal.
小丑克拉比的
最喜欢的一餐。
We want Krabby!
我们想要蟹蟹！
Where is Krabby,
Mr. Krabs?
克拉比在哪里
蟹老板？
He'll be here after
I count their money.
他稍后会在这里
我数着他们的钱。
Just stall them.
只是拖延他们。
Stall them?
How do I do that?
阻止他们？
我该怎么做？
I don't know, be entertaining.
不知道，娱乐一下吧
Duh-uh... duh.
呃呃……呃。
Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
You're not Krabby the Clown.
你不是小丑克拉比。
No, I'm not. I'm, uh...
不，我不是。我是，呃…
I'm Krabby's beloved sidekick
我是克拉比最亲爱的伙伴
the Krabby Patty... Burglar.
克拉比·帕蒂……窃贼。
Lame.
瘸。
Krabby will be here soon.
克拉比很快就会来。
He, uh, had to take the bus.
他，呃，必须坐公共汽车。
But in the meantime,
let's have some fun!
但与此同时，
让我们玩得开心吧！
You kids like bubbles?
小朋友们喜欢泡泡吗？
No.
不。
Well, you've never
seen my bubbles.
嗯，你从来没有
看到了我的泡泡。
Voila!
瞧！
A bubble shaped
like a jellyfish.
呈气泡状
像水母一样。
How about that?
怎么样？
Still lame.
还是蹩脚。
Okay.
好的。
Prepare to be blown back
on your tail fins.
准备好被吹回来
在你的尾鳍上。
Ta-dah!
哒哒！
Uh. Uh.
呃。呃。
You stink!
你太臭了！
Bring on the clown!
带上小丑吧！
Okay.
好的。
Now for a finale.
现在是结局。
Boo!
嘘！
My eyes!
我的眼睛！
Whoa-oh-oh!
哇哦哦！
They seem to respond
to me being in pain.
他们似乎有回应
对我来说是痛苦的。
They enjoy
other people's misery.
他们享受
别人的痛苦。
Hey, kids.
Check this out.
嘿，孩子们。
看看这个。
I've got them
right where I want them.
我有它们
就在我想要它们的地方。
Aah!
啊啊！
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
噢！噢！噢！噢！
Ooh! Yow! Ow! Ooh! Yow!
哦！哟！噢！哦！哟！
Mr. Krabs
蟹老板先生
I can't take much more
of this stalling stuff.
我无法承受更多
这些停滞不前的东西。
Always thinking about yourself.
总是为自己着想。
Get out there and stall!
出去并停下来！
What happened to your arms
and legs, boy?
你的手臂怎么了
还有腿，孩子？
The kids are using
them as boomerangs.
孩子们正在使用
他们就像回旋镖。
Boomerangs?
回旋镖？
Oh, no!
They might break my windows.
哦，不！
他们可能会打破我的窗户。
What are we going to do?
我们要做什么？
Well, now that all
their money's counted
好吧，现在这一切
他们的钱被计算在内
tell them Krabby
has just arrived.
告诉他们克拉比
刚刚抵达。
Really? He's here?
真的吗？他来了？
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh,
boy, oh, boy, oh, boy...
哦，男孩，哦，男孩，哦，
男孩，哦，男孩，哦，男孩……
Get out there and tell them!
出去告诉他们！
Listen, everybody.
听着，大家。
Krabby the Clown
is in the building!
小丑克拉比
就在大楼里！
Who do you want?!
你想要谁？！
Krabby!
蟹蟹！
When do you want him?!
你什么时候要他？！
Now!
现在！
Krabby! Krabby!
蟹蟹！蟹蟹！
Krabby! Krabby! Hooray!
蟹蟹！蟹蟹！万岁！
Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
Are you ready to meet
Krabby the Clown?
你准备好见面了吗
小丑克拉比？
Yay!
耶！
All right. Here you go!
好的。干得好！
Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
Uh, thank you all for coming.
呃，谢谢大家的到来。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Eat plenty of Krabby Patties.
多吃蟹肉饼。
♪ Doo-doo, dee-doodly-doo
♪ 嘟嘟，嘟嘟嘟
♪ Doo-doo, dee-doo.
♪ 嘟嘟，嘟嘟。
Ah, Krabs, you'd done it again.
啊，蟹蟹，你又这么做了。
I'll say you have.
我会说你有。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
How could you, Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板，你怎么能这样呢？
You promised these children
Krabby the Clown.
你答应过这些孩子
小丑克拉比。
But all I saw up there was...
但我在上面看到的只是...
Cheapy the Cheapskate.
便宜的小气鬼。
Hey, I ain't cheap.
嘿嘿，我可不便宜。
Now take this tomato
back to the kitchen
before it spoils.
现在拿这个西红柿
回到厨房
在它变质之前。
But what about
the true meaning of summer?
但是呢
夏天的真正意义？
What about the children?
孩子们呢？
The children?
孩子们？
I don't care about the children.
我不关心孩子们。
I just care about
their parents' money.
我只关心
他们父母的钱。
Ah, the fact that their feeble
minds are easily manipulated
啊，事实上他们的软弱
思想很容易被操纵
by cheap playgrounds
and talentless clowns
便宜的游乐场
和没有才华的小丑
is no skin off my nose.
我的鼻子没有皮肤脱落。
Survival of the fittest,
SpongeBob.
适者生存，
海绵宝宝。
Survival of the fittest.
Heh-heh.
适者生存。
呵呵。
Oh. Hey, kids.
哦。嘿，孩子们。
Uh... Uncle Krabs
has to go to the bank now.
呃……蟹蟹叔叔
现在必须去银行。
Get him!
抓住他！
I suppose I'll never know
the true meaning of summer.
我想我永远不会知道
夏天的真正意义。
I thought I knew it once
我以为我曾经知道过
but that was a long,
long time ago.
但那是一个漫长的、
很久以前。
You mean this morning?
你是说今天早上吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Come outside, Mr. Squarepants.
出来吧，方裤先生。
It's a summer miracle.
这是夏天的奇迹。
Hoorah!
万岁！
Wow, thousands of dollars
fluttering in the breeze.
哇，几千块钱
在微风中飘扬。
I guess that's the true
meaning of summer.
我想这就是事实
夏天的意义。
Where's Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板在哪里？
He's missing out
on all the summer fun.
他错过了
整个夏天的乐趣。
Let me go!
让我走吧！
I got to get some
of that green stuff.
我得买一些
那些绿色的东西。
No!
不！
Not that green stuff!
不是那种绿色的东西！
No!!
不！！
Ah, finally, the weekend is here
啊，终于，周末来了
and this isn't just
any old weekend.
这不仅仅是
任何旧周末。
This is the weekend SpongeBob
and Patrick go camping.
这是海绵宝宝的周末
和帕特里克去露营。
Wouldn't it be great
if they got lost in the woods
这不是很棒吗
如果他们在树林里迷路了
and never came back?
然后再也没有回来？
Patrick, I'm scared.
帕特里克，我很害怕。
Ho-ho, that would be great.
呵呵，那就太好了。
You've waited
a long time for this.
你已经等了
这已经很长时间了。
A soft bed...
柔软的床...
Warm tea...
温茶...
A good book...
一本好书...
And two whole days with no.
整整两天没有。
What the...?
什么……？
SpongeBob... aren't you two
海绵宝宝……你们两个不是吗
supposed to be camping?
应该去露营吗？
We arecamping.
我们正在露营。
SpongeBob, it's not camping
海绵宝宝，这不是露营
if you're ten feet
from your house.
如果你有十英尺
从你家。
It doesn't matter where you are
你在哪里并不重要
as long as you're outdoors.
只要你在户外。
While all those soft city folk
are safe in their beds
虽然所有那些温柔的城里人
在床上很安全
reading books, we're out
here pitting ourselves
看书，我们出去了
这里坑我们自己
against the formidable
forces of nature.
对抗强大的
自然的力量。
You want to join us?
你想加入我们吗？
No.
不。
Okay. Have fun inside.
好的。里面玩得开心。
What do you mean,
have fun inside?
你是什么意思，
里面玩得开心吗？
Just...
have fun inside.
只是...
里面玩得开心。
See you tomorrow.
明天见。
Oh. Bye.
哦。再见。
You little sneak.
你这个小鬼鬼祟祟的。
I see what
you're doing. What?
我明白了什么
你正在做。什么？
Don't think I can't
see what you're doing.
别以为我不能
看看你在做什么。
What?
什么？
You're saying I can't take it.
你说我受不了。
But all I...
但我所有...
You're saying I'm soft.
你说我心软。
You think your little
"have fun inside" challenge
你以为你的小
“在里面玩得开心”挑战
is going to make me
come camping with you
会让我
和你一起露营
but that is
never going to happen.
但那就是
永远不会发生。
There's no way I'm going
to sit out here all night
我没有办法去
坐在这里整晚
with you two losers.
和你们两个失败者在一起。
So get used to it.
所以要习惯它。
Okay.
好的。
Have fun inside.
里面玩得开心。
That's it!
I'm in!
就是这样！
我进来了！
I'll show you camping.
我会带你去露营。
Squidward's going to come
camping with us.
章鱼哥要来了
和我们一起露营。
Now you'll see how a real...
现在你会看到真正的...
outdoorsman does it.
户外人士做到了。
Here we are...
My remote-controlled
我们在这里...
我的遥控
self-assembling tent.
自组装帐篷。
Watch and learn.
观看并学习。
That was great, Squidward
太棒了，章鱼哥
but how do you get inside?
但你怎么进去呢？
Yeah, it's all crushy-looking.
是的，一切都看起来很破碎。
It isn't put up yet, you idiots.
还没放出来呢，你们这些白痴。
Customization.
定制。
Genius.
天才。
He's tenderizing the ground.
他正在使地面变得柔软。
Of course.
当然。
Write that down,
write that down!
写下来，
把它写下来！
Huh?
啊？
Voila.
瞧。
But what could compare to just
lying out under the stars?
但还有什么能比得上
躺在星空下？
Well, Iworked up an appetite
嗯，我食欲大开
as big as all outdoors.
和所有户外的一样大。
Time for a little grub.
是时候吃点东西了。
I suppose you two
are going to stew up
我想你们两个
会炖起来
some twigs and rocks, right?
一些树枝和石头，对吗？
No, we got something
even better...
不，我们有东西
甚至更好...
Marshmallows.
棉花糖。
Mmm-mm.
嗯嗯。
Just like the astronauts eat.
就像宇航员吃东西一样。
Patrick to SpongeBob.
帕特里克对海绵宝宝。
Do you read me? Over.
你读懂我了吗？超过。
SpongeBob to Patrick.
海绵宝宝对帕特里克。
I read you. Over.
我读懂了你。超过。
Patrick to SpongeBob.
帕特里克对海绵宝宝。
I like going.
我喜欢去。
Over.
超过。
SpongeBob to Patrick.
海绵宝宝对帕特里克。
Me, too.
我也是。
SpongeBob to Patrick,
help yourself. Over.
海绵宝宝对帕特里克，
帮助自己。超过。
Yummy.
好吃。
Patrick to SpongeBob.
帕特里克对海绵宝宝。
The deliciousness has landed.
美味已经落地。
Well, you two astronauts
can eat marshmallows.
好吧，你们两个宇航员
可以吃棉花糖。
I'm going to have a can
我要有一罐
of Swedish barnacle balls...
just as soon
瑞典藤壶球...
尽快
as I can get my can opener.
因为我可以拿到我的开罐器。
But, Squidward
但是，章鱼哥
didn't you take a can opener
你没拿开罐器吗
when you hiked out here?
你什么时候来这里徒步的？
Why would I bother?
我为什么要打扰？
We're ten feet from my house.
我们离我家十英尺。
But this is the wilderness.
但这是荒野。
It just doesn't seem to
fit the camping spirit.
只是似乎没有
符合露营精神。
Pretty weenie.
漂亮的维尼。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Give me a marshmallow.
给我一块棉花糖。
Ha-ha-ha.
哈哈哈。
Okay, besides spitting
molten foodstuffs at me
好吧，除了吐口水
融化的食物在我身上
what else do you do for fun?
你还做什么好玩的事？
Well... after a long day
of camping
好吧...经过漫长的一天
露营的
it's nice to unwind with
a nice, relaxing campfire song.
很高兴与您一起放松
一首优美、轻松的篝火歌曲。
I call this one
"The Campfire Song Song."
我称这个为
《篝火歌》。
♪ Let's gather round
the campfire ♪
♪ 让我们围成一圈
篝火♪
♪ And sing our
campfire song ♪
♪ 唱我们的
篝火歌♪
♪ Our C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E
S-O-N-G song ♪
♪ 我们的 C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E
S-O-N-G 歌曲 ♪
♪ And if you don't think
that we can sing it ♪
♪ 如果你不这么认为
我们可以唱它♪
♪ Faster, then you're wrong
♪ 更快，那你就错了
♪ But it'll help
if you just sing along... ♪
♪ 但这会有帮助
如果你只是跟着唱...♪
♪ Bom, bom, bom
♪ 嘭，嘭，嘭
♪ C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E
S-O-N-G song ♪
S-O-N-G 歌曲 ♪
♪ C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E
S-O-N-G song ♪
S-O-N-G 歌曲 ♪
♪ And if you don't
think that we ♪
♪ 如果你不这样做
认为我们♪
♪ Can sing it faster,
then you are wrong ♪
♪ 唱得更快，
那你就错了♪
♪ But it'll help
if you just sing along... ♪
♪ 但这会有帮助
如果你只是跟着唱...♪
♪ C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E
S-O-N-G song ♪ Patrick!
S-O-N-G 歌曲 ♪ 帕特里克！
♪ Song. C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E...
♪ 歌曲。营火...
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
Good.
好的。
♪ It'll help...
♪ 这会有所帮助...
♪ If you just sing along...
♪ 只要你跟着唱...
♪ Oh, yeah!
♪ 哦，是的！
Now, wasn't that relaxing?
现在，这不是很放松吗？
No.
不。
Thisis relaxing.
这很放松。
Oh, no!
哦，不！
I'll save you, Squidward.
我会救你的，章鱼哥。
Squidward, are you all right?
章鱼哥，你还好吗？
That's it.
就是这样。
Chew... chew...
and swallow.
嚼……嚼……
并吞下。
There. Better?
那里。更好的？
Better?!
更好的？！
I was just fine
until you launched
我很好
直到你启动
that ballistic junk food
into my windpipe!
弹道垃圾食品
进入我的气管！
But I had to. It's
too dangerous
但我不得不这么做。这是
太危险了
to play the clarinet badly
out here in the wilderness.
单簧管吹得不好
在这荒野里。
It might attract...
可能会吸引...
a sea bear.
一只海熊。
A sea bear?
海熊？
You mean like the ones
that... don't exist?!
你的意思是像那些
那……不存在？！
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
There's no such thing.
没有这样的事。
They're just a myth.
它们只是一个神话。
Oh, no, Squidward.
哦，不，章鱼哥。
Sea bears are all too real.
海熊太真实了。
It says so in the
Bikini Bottom Inquirer.
它是这样说的
比基尼泳裤询问者。
"I married a Sea Bear"?
“我嫁给了一只海熊”？
Yeah, and Fake Science Monthly.
是的，还有《假科学月刊》。
"Sea Bears and
Fairytales Are Real"?
“海熊和
童话是真的吗”
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
这是最愚蠢的事
我曾经听说过。
Well, maybe it isstupid
好吧，也许这很愚蠢
but it's also dumb.
但这也是愚蠢的。
Patrick's right, Squidward...
帕特里克是对的，章鱼哥……
Sea Bears are
no laughing matter.
海熊是
没什么好笑的。
Why, once I met this guy
who knew this guy
为什么，一旦我遇到这个人
谁认识这个人
who knew this guy
who knew this guy's cousin...
谁认识这个人的表弟...
You're right!
你说得对！
I should be more careful.
我应该更加小心。
In fact, why don't you tell me
事实上，你为什么不告诉我
all of the things I shouldn't do
所有我不应该做的事情
if I want to keep
the sea bears away.
如果我想保留
大海远去。
Okay, that's easy.
好吧，这很容易。
First off,
don't play the clarinet.
首先，
不要吹单簧管。
Okay, then what?
好吧，然后呢？
Never wave your flashlight
back and forth really fast.
切勿挥动手电筒
来回真的很快。
Flashlights are
their natural prey.
手电筒是
他们的天然猎物。
You're kidding.
你开玩笑吧。
Don't stomp around...
They take that
别乱踩...
他们认为
as a challenge.
Yeah.
作为一个挑战。
是的。
Go on.
继续。
Don't ever eat cheese.
永远不要吃奶酪。
Sliced or cubed?
切片还是切块？
Cubed. Sliced is fine.
立方体。切片就好了
Yeah, yeah. And?
是啊是啊。和？
Never wear a sombrero......in
a goofy fashion.
永远不要戴宽边帽......
一种愚蠢的时尚。
Or clown shoes.
Or a hoop
skirt.
或者小丑鞋。
或者一个铁环
裙子。
And never...
Ever...
并且从来没有...
曾经...
Ever!
Duh!
曾经！
呃！
Screech like a chimpanzee!
像黑猩猩一样尖叫！
Wow. It's amazing
哇。太神奇了
how many things
can set a sea bear off.
有多少东西
可以引爆海熊。
They're horrible.
他们太可怕了。
And... and suddenly,
I have the sense
然后……突然间，
我有感觉
we're all in danger.
我们都处于危险之中。
Why?
为什么？
I don't know...
我不知道...
Just a feeling!
只是一种感觉！
No.
不。
Yes.
是的。
No.
不。
Squidward, please don't.
章鱼哥，请别这样。
SpongeBob, what are
we going to do?
海绵宝宝，什么是
我们要做什么？
A sea bear is sure
to come and eat us.
海熊是肯定的
来吃我们。
Don't worry, Patrick.
别担心，帕特里克。
I'll draw us an anti-sea bear
circle in the dirt.
我会画一只反海熊
在泥土中画圈。
Good thinking.
好想法。
All the experts say
所有专家都说
it's the only defense
against a sea bear attack.
这是唯一的防御
抵御海熊的攻击。
Ha-ha-ha-ha. You guys
are so gullible.
哈哈哈。你们
太容易受骗了。
See? I did everything
that attracts a sea bear
看？我做了一切
吸引海熊的
and nothing happened.
但什么也没发生。
If sea bears really exist,
why didn't one show up?
如果海熊真的存在
为什么没有人出现？
Maybe it's because
you're not wearing
也许是因为
你没穿
your sombrero
in a goofy fashion.
你的宽边帽
以一种愚蠢的方式。
Oh, pfft. Sorry.
哦，噗。对不起。
How silly of me.
我真傻。
You mean like this?
你的意思是这样吗？
No. Like that.
不，就像这样。
Squidward, are you okay?
章鱼哥，你还好吗？
No.
不。
Quick. Jump inside our
anti-sea bear circle
快的。跳进我们的
防海熊圈
before he comes back.
在他回来之前。
Yeah. Sea bears
often attack
more than once.
是的。海熊
经常攻击
不止一次。
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
A dirt circle won't
stop that monster.
污垢圈不会
阻止那个怪物。
I'm running for my life.
我正在为我的生命而奔跑。
No!
不！
Don't run! Sea
bears hate that.
别跑！海
熊讨厌这样。
Thanks for the tip.
谢谢你的提示。
I guess I'll just
limp home, then.
我想我只会
那么，跛行回家吧。
No!
不！
They hate limping
more than running!
他们讨厌跛行
比跑步更重要！
Well, I guess I'll just have...
好吧，我想我只会...
I should have warned you
about crawling.
我应该警告你的
关于爬行。
What did I do that time?
我当时做了什么？
I don't know. I guess
he just doesn't like you.
我不知道。我猜
他只是不喜欢你。
Pretend to be somebody else.
假装成别人。
Here, draw a circle.
在这里，画一个圆圈。
Okay.
好的。
That was an oval!
那是一个椭圆形！
It has to be a circle!
一定是一个圆！
Move over!
移过去！
Hey. It worked.
嘿。它起作用了。
You guys saved my life.
你们救了我的命。
Yeah. I'm glad it was
just a sea bear.
是的。我很高兴这是
只是一只海熊。
This circle would never
hold back a sea rhinoceros.
这个圈子永远不会
挡住海犀。
What attracts them?
是什么吸引他们？
The sound of a sea bear attack.
海熊攻击的声音。
Huh. Good thing
we're all wearing
呵呵。好东西
我们都穿着
our anti-sea
rhinoceros
undergarments.
我们的反海
犀牛
内衣。
Right, Squidward?
对吧，章鱼哥？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道